worldmarte.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy final clean-Worldmarte.com

### Privacy policy

This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of the Worldmart*E ("The Wordmart*E" or "Worldmart*E") services and the Worldmart*E website ("The Site" or "Site") and the collection, use, processing of your Collected Information by Worldmart*E website. By using this Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy set out below. All terms not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use Agreement between you and Worldmart*E which by use of this Site you agree to accept. 

If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at support@worldmartE.com. 

**1.Special Considerations for minors**

If you are under 18 years old, you are not allowed to use our services, All of our users and members are required to be 18 years or older . 

**2.User name and password**

When you plan to register as a member, we ask you to select a user name and password, but also to provide a password hint question and answer so that when you lost your password, we can still confirm your identity. You can only use your password to access your account. If you leak the password, you may lose your personally identifiable information and possible adverse consequences to you. Therefore, for any reason endangers the safety of your password, you should immediately contact us at support@worldmartE.com. 

**3.Registration Information**

When you register as a member, we ask you to fill out a registration form. You are required to provide your company name, company location, business type, and main product categories of your company. In addition, you also required to provide the real name, phone number and e-mail address of your company contact person. If you apply for Gold or above membership type, you are required to provide additional information. Those information may include the scan copy of your company's business license, a brief description of services and products of your company, the referee company’s name, phone number, email of the contact person and your Trade Association ID. We will use these data to verify the identity of our members, and strictly control the access threshold for a member of the industry to improve Web site security of member information. Information will be use to notify new services and opportunities for our targeted members.

**4.Information We Collect**

**  Transaction Information**

When you list a diamond for sale, purchase or sell a diamond, or use the Services in any way, we record information related to each transaction, including the amount of the transaction. We retain this information for each of your transactions through Worldmart*E website. 

**  Information About You From Third Parties**

In order to protect us and our members against potential fraud, we may verify with third parties the information you provide. In the course of such verification, we receive personally identifiable information about you from such services. This may include background and credit checks by obtaining information about you and your business from a credit bureau or a business information service such as Dun & Bradstreet or bank. If you incur a debt to Worldmart*E, we will generally conduct a credit check by obtaining additional information about you from a credit bureau, to the extent permitted by law. Worldmart*E, at its sole discretion, also reserves the right periodically to retrieve and review a business and / or consumer credit report for any account, and reserves the right to close an account based on information obtained during this credit review process. 

**  Additional Verification**

If we cannot verify the information that you provide we may ask you to send us additional information by fax (such as your drivers' license, credit card statement, and/or a recent utility bill or other information linking you to the applicable address), or to answer additional questions online to help verify your information.

**5.Information Users Obtain**

**  Your Use of Information and Our Services**

In order to facilitate the transactions between Worldmart*E members, our Service allows you limited access to other users' contact or shipping information. As a member you may have access to the User ID, email address and other contact or shipping information of other members. By consenting to the applicable Terms of Service, you agree that, with respect to other users' personally identifiable information that you obtain through the site or through an Worldmart*E-related communication or Worldmart*E-facilitated transaction, you will only use this information for: (a) Worldmart*E-related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, (b) using services offered through Worldmart*E (e.g. diamond sales, shipping or insurance), and (c) any other purpose that such user expressly agrees to after adequate disclosure of the purpose(s). In all cases, you must provide users with the opportunity to remove them from your database and review any information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this Section, you cannot disclose personally identifiable information about another Worldmart*E user to any third party without our consent and the consent of such other user after adequate disclosure. Note that law enforcement personnel and other rights holders are given different rights with respect to information they access. Worldmart*E does not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you may not add a Worldmart*E user to your mail list (email or physical mail) without their expressed consent after adequate disclosure, even if said user has previously made a purchase from you. We strictly enforce our Anti-Spam Policy. To report-related spam, please send an email to: support@worldmarte.com.

**6.Cookies**

We use "cookies" to store specific information about you and track your visits to our Site. It is not uncommon for websites to use cookies to enhance identification of their users. A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can be sent to your computer's hard drive only if you access our Site using the computer. If you do not de-activate or erase the cookie, each time you use the same computer to access our Site, our web servers will be notified of your visit to our Site and in turn we may have knowledge of your visit and the pattern of your usage. Generally, we use cookies to identify you and enable us to access your Registration Information, Publishing Information or Payment Information so you do not have to re-enter it; gather statistical information about usage by Users; research visiting patters and help target advertisements based on User interests; assist our partners to track User visits to the Site and process orders; and track progress and participation in promotions. 

You can determine if and how a cookie will be accepted by configuring your browser's which is installed in the computer you are using to access the Site. If you desire, you can change those configurations in your browser. By setting your preferences in the browser, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is sent, or you can reject all cookies. If you reject all cookies by choosing the cookie-disabling function in your browser, you may be required to re-enter your information on our Site more often and certain features of our Site may be unavailable. 

**7.Disclosure and use of information**

Member information may be shared only if you have permitted us to do so. We also offer you the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.

We will carry out comprehensive statistical data of the identity and transactions of you and (or) your company then disclose some reasonable content to advertisers. However, in these circumstances, we will not disclose any of these organizations who may be used to identify the user's personally identifiable information. 

You agree that we may disclose or use your personal information for the identification and (or) to confirm your identity, or resolve disputes, or help to ensure site security, limit fraud, illegal or other criminal activities, to implement our service agreement.

You agree that we may disclose or use your personal information to protect your life, property, safety or to prevent serious violations of the legal rights of others or for the needs of the public interest. 

You agree that we may disclose or use your personal information to improve our services and make our services to better meet your requirements, so that when you use our services better experience. 

You agree that we use your personal information to contact you and provide you with information of interest to you, such as: product information, agency services. You accept the "Services Agreement" and agree with this Privacy policy shall receive such information.

Our website users to submit product information and pricing, and gold members and diamond members can search for members of these quotes and product information. 

When we forced by law or in accordance with the Government or by rights of persons suspected of violations by identifying the request and provide your information, we will disclose your information in good faith. 

**Information storage and exchange of**

Collect user information and data will be stored in the server of Worldmarte.com and related companies. 

**8.Special Warning to Users in communities**

Users are warned that disclosing personally identifiable information online through communities makes the information submitted public information; such disclosure may increase the chance of receiving "spam" or unsolicited e-mail. Users should be extra careful and to use their discretion when disclosing information online.

**9.External links**

This website contains links to other sites. Worldmart*E is not responsible for the privacy protection measures of the sites. We may need to increase business partners or co-branded site at any time.

**10.Public Information**

Your trade items posted for information or quotes will be displayed partially in public areas whereas members of the Gold and Diamond members will receive the information in full. All public information will not contain any personal information of your company nor trade transaction unless it is disclosed for your own company marketing and promotion purpose. 

**11.Security Measures**

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information. 

As a Registered User, your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

**12.Disclaimers**

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

**13.The right to modify**

Worldmart*E reserves the right to change this or any policy of exclusive rights. Any change of our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice about the new policy on the site notice. Any change has an immediate effect. In any case duplicate policy to the latest version as authority. Therefore, please check for changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the website of drilling any data exchange will be deemed your agreement with the latest evidence of the privacy policy. 

**14.Contact us**

If you have any problems in the use of any comments and suggestions, please contact us: support@worldmartE.com
